Please introduce yourself.
Hi there, I'm Yoshio Sakuma. Pleased to meet you.
Origin of the name? Where does your name come from? Hello, I'm Yusei Sakuma, nice to meet you.
Where did the name come from?
Name origin...
I don't know.
Yes, sir.
From all around...
Massa or something.
These days it's called a massa.
I'm from Tokyo, Japan.
Birthday March 19, 2006
Blood type B.
My favorite part of my face.
After all, isn't that a smile?
mouth of a (sword) sheath
Is this the size of the room?
Hobby is basketball
I've done it from first grade through sixth grade.
I also do it in private.
special skill
Rubik's Cube and
I'm waiting for you to make me do it with a rolled door and a finig.
Tell us something interesting.
Ooh.
Well, then...
imitation (of someone, something)
It's not funny to begin with, but I...
Kay Boca Kes monomaniac of "I'm going to go out..."? It's not funny to begin with, but I'll go for it.
K of Bokeh.
I like Bokeh.
This is Oompa Loompa's
Favorite food
Hamburg.
He said he couldn't eat fish to begin with.
I'm limited to meat.
I came up with the hamburger.
It was limited to school lunches at elementary schools, which led to the hamburger steak.
It's pretty much a school lunch at elementary schools and the like.
You eat everything.
That's where it all started, didn't it?
My dislike of fish is
Favorite color
for quite a long time
I'm saying blue.
Lately, I've been a little...
I'm starting to like green a bit.
One of my strong points.
You mean that I will concentrate like this?
disadvantage
It's because I'm so focused on that one thing that I'm going against the grain.
I think the disadvantage is that I sometimes lose sight of my surroundings.
way of saying
I think it's a shortcoming that I used to say that I was probably a bit more reluctant to say things like that a while ago.
I was a little lost. He said something about reluctance.
most attractive feature of a person
Well, yeah.
Smile, isn't it? Smile, after all.
after
triad
Where we want to fix it.
Surprisingly, I'm quite shy.
What made you laugh the most recently?
I just did, you know, Mr. Oompa Loomp's
That was something that made me laugh so hard.
Recent problems?
Sometimes it's like a turning point or something.
When something changes.
Oops!
Are you having trouble? Masai Masai, yes, I'm doing 100 questions right now.
Yes, we're doing 100 questions each now too.
You're doing 100 questions each?
How many questions are you on?
Twenty questions now.
You shouldn't have done that at all.
Genki Masaya.
I'm fine.
I'm a little too energetic and a little injured.
How are you, Masaya?
How are you, Masaya? How are you? How are you?
Yes, I'm fine.
Good to see you.
Oh, it's great!
Happy Lucky?
birthday
Why not?
Yes, it is.
Yes, sir.
Oh, well...
It's like when the environment changes.
Sometimes it's just not good.
Yes, that's one of my problems.
routine
I have a group of YouTubers that I like.
You see it there, every day.
Only one of the uninhabited islands
I'm thinking more of the fire on the desert island, or the match version.
If I could only use one thing for my home energy
I definitely want a middle school institute or something like that.
Well, maybe you simply have a weak morning.
Its really not going to happen.
Sleep until the last minute.
Maybe do a video of the rehearsal at Spanspawn.
I'd like to do something like that.
If you won the Shichi-Go-San Kake Okada lottery, what would you spend it on?
House and car.
G-Class Lens
It's really been a long time.
oxygen
stress reduction technique
move
If I sweat or something, I'm all over it.
I forget everything.
treasure
You are an observer, after all.
Earliest memory
three wheeler
The oldest tricycle ride near my house.
Memory.
Can I ask you to play air guitar?
Air guitar?
Is there such a thing?
Air guitar? Is there such a thing? Air guitar?
Is everything okay? Who is the nicest person in reality?
It's not going to change.
I think about it a lot when it occurs to me.
Aaargh!
I'm going to do that here.
On the other hand, the toughest
Surprisingly, I'm in this writer.
something
It's very tough sometimes.
The nature of the craft.
That's why.
If you're being a little harsh.
They're being harsher than that.
which makes me feel like ...
Unexpected aspect
That's what makes the crafting really solid.
It's like, "I'm not thinking about anything.
Surprisingly great evolution already!
I think I heard the most lies in reality.
Absolute numbers.
It's already a little bit like some kind of episodic talk or something.
I'm so good at what I do, I'm backstage. I'm sure there are a lot of them. I'm not sure if it's the episode talk or something else.
I don't know, I'm just too good at it.
I can't tell if it's real or fake anymore.
We're in that realm, I'm in that realm.
What are they?
I don't know what kind of existence
I wish I could be the one to inspire the unexpected.
secret
I'm the one who doesn't ask for secrets.
Wait a minute, wait a minute, wait a minute for Sato, for my friends at school and so on.
tolerable
I'm going to dance.
In the end, members of the group
It's because they dance for us.
It makes me want to dance with my friends at school.
Short-term concentration is
Probably as good as anyone else's.
I feel like someone I'd like to meet.
I'd like to meet number one.
(it doesn't matter what) anything is OK
I want to feel the greatness of the number one person right in front of me.
current kick
Bathroom.
I feel wonderful at all times.
Even if your body is not tired for a long time, it is still nice to take a bath at that time.
Even if your body is not tired.
A bath would feel good.
I will never forget this feeling.
Off is definitely not out anymore.
I'm definitely going to be with someone else.
I do sports in the morning or something.
I'm really disturbed Black is cute, and you can see that when you look at the pictures of him as a child.
I was just thinking that it's pretty neat.
Something about a TV show...
Like Mr. Toro's singing and rapping.
I like that one. If it were to die tomorrow.
A very large scale live concert venue.
I want to go live.
With cheers from the crowd
with a bang
I'd like to be gone.
If I were to be reborn...
I like cicadas.
I mean, those two weeks have been crazy hot.
I'm sure it's very dense.
One Kanji character?
shady online money-making
straw
bank
I go to the big map and play with the animals.
It depends on what you are looking for.
But I think I'm also quite a drag.
What's a fish? The kind of emoji you get when you smile.
A lot of them were on this face.
Here is a question from a fan
I see
What is your favorite outfit?
At the arena.
Clothes when cats and milk and sugar
Don't go in there when they're dancing.
What's your favorite portion of rice balls?
Plum.
What's important to you?
sensation
I know it's recent, but seriously, I'm trying to be positive.
Constant negative time.
I've been thinking about it lately.
What is your favorite phrase in the part you sang?
Diamond Lily's rusty
Laughing and laughing with you, I rise in this lonely night
He always wants everyone to laugh as well.
I think it's better to sing "Smile, Smile, Smile" as a ballad.
What was your favorite event at the gymnastics festival?
Is it a total competition?
reward
Food that makes you feel happy the moment you eat it.
My favorite song in the choreography?
Mr. Android.
I felt like I was having a lot of fun when I was dancing this.
I'm hungry.
I was pretty hungry.
ramen
7 days
thrill
Make it a perfect 7 days.
Day 1 Sky Didi
2nd day
The most of foreign
Great exclamations!
3rd day
I'd like to do a thrilling seven days in a haunted place like that, with a lot of screaming and a new moon bot on the third day.
So that's the thrill of it.
I'd like to do something like that.
If the members are family.
What will the family structure be?
Takato sect (of Shin Buddhism)
I'm a mother.
Jun.
I'm a father.
any turtle (esp. the Japanese pond turtle, Kaname, or Kaname's turtle, Kaname)
She's the big sister, Gosaku is the big brother, Kaname is the big sister, and Kosaka is the big brother.
indicates certainty, emphasis, etc.
At the same age.
Cuz.
Ryo and the younger one.
is
Classroom seating is
Basically, absolutely backwards.
Right.
Or in the middle of the back.
I'm pretty much looking around at everyone.
Walk in the local section and you'll get cramped
How are you?
hmm
I knew it was this space.
I lost track of time.
Let's get up on the stage and forget about the time.
2nd, I'll stand up.
This is really bad. This is really bad.
If we compare the members to oden green, we can compare them to oden goo.
A good harvest is a good harvest is a good harvest is a good harvest is a good harvest is a good harvest is a good harvest
Kazuto is a radish. Jun is a radish.
Beef sinew?
So, Takada...
Uh...
Oh, kelp! It's so random...
It's so random.
Well, if you could change it from gym and members, what color would it be?
No, pink is totally fine.
What's your favorite picture book? On the Grid Hula.
Local charm? Lots of personality and loudness.
I doubt that
Which songs are fun to sing?
I kind of like piston androids, dancing and singing.
On the contrary, the song is quite challenging.
Please use your favorite emoji with your face.
Eh, that, um, but I can't do it.
Um, eyes, I hope this happens.
Today's breakfast is a fifth-car cut.
Can I go to YouTube, um...
Required
iron (content)
If you were not a singer-actor or musician, what would you be?
No, it could have been really bad.
I wonder what would have happened to me if I had not done this activity.
Sometimes I get scared.
There is a theory that it might be very good.
I don't think it's impossible.
Stimulation?
Naa Ryota's rehearsal song at the arena.
It was something amazing.
I thought, "Oh, wow.
Do you wonder what you would be if you were an animal?
I keep saying red panda.
I don't really see the resemblance.
Well, I'll leave it at that, just in case.
Wow, I'm switching back and forth for a day.
Some people are video artists.
I want to experience it for real once.
The world of that video.
I guess that's what I meant.
The biggest part is the biggest part.
Where that number of visitors is the largest.
Embracer!
People I admire.
Takumi Kitamura, right?
Movies I want to see these days
this
Tokyo Revengers.
I saw the destiny.
I didn't go to the decisive battle.
I want to see a decisive battle.
The clothes are, you know.
Stylish in a single piece
Don't lie to me.
earnest
be genuine
This is already this year.
I think I'm going to take it to the extreme.
You're just saying that again.
No, it's not.
No, sir.
Let's go shopping for clothes together.
Yes, you can buy them at the bakery.
Sometimes I'm surprised at the amazing chus and other times I'm surprised at the amazing chus.
My appeal points
I'm kind of, you know...
Cool and cute.
these two
Funny thing I saw a dog in town.
Being able to eat dinner at 7:30 at night.
Well, why not?
Being able to get up at 5:30.
source of energy
My goals are the source of my energy.
It won't be this one.
Side dish?
Is a salad usually a side dish?
At the deli, yes.
What song would you say is your favorite?
YouTube.
Ojens is... er...
What was that?
Microbe, microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe microbe
like you would if you saw it.
that's right
a person of
On the contrary, I hate it.
Like fish.
Which seat do you prefer on the Shinkansen?
I like the outside, even these days.
From the inside
Now?
this
But I kind of like it in the House.
Recently learned foreign words?
I'm not quite sure how to pronounce it.
Like an indage.
Like blowing like indage like blowing like blowing.
The pronunciation is a little wrinkled.
Yes, sir.
The name of the sitter.
I want to be someone who leaves history in this world.
It's been this way for a long time.
I want you to decide from when I was in the bath in the second grade.
My favorite recent photo
Feeling since the bath during the music video shoot at Shakespeare's. My favorite photo I took recently.
Shakespearean time mv shooting during the middle 7 of the
Photo: Gas.
What happens when you feel happy in winter? I love winter so much.
Songs like Illuminations.
What is the best tool for restraining yourself?
Once-in-a-lifetime sports I'm good at
basketball
What is the most impressive dream you had while sleeping?
Mario's dossier fell on top of himself.
When I woke up, I was like, "Oh my God.
When I was a little girl, my dream for the future was...
Maybe he was a bus driver.
Coffee drinker? Tea drinker?
Oh, it's already tea.
I love tea so much these days!
My favorite donuts are the ones sprinkled with chocolate puffs.
My specialty is pasta.
The one I'm about to make that I want to challenge myself with, my specialty dish is pasta.
Challenges
How many of those can you have that you can accomplish in a short period of time?
Which current resident's song would you most like people to listen to?
this
I wish Diamond Rue would listen to it.
this year
Um...
I mean, maybe it's okay.
Maybe I'd like to increase, you know, something like that.
That's the thing, I hope we can do something with the YouTube project.
Last.
A word to those watching.
I'm going to keep making everyone happy!
Thank you for your hard work.